<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on &#34;Like punning, programming is a play on words.&#34; -Alan Perlis</title>
    <link>https://austinletson.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on &#34;Like punning, programming is a play on words.&#34; -Alan Perlis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://austinletson.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Spine: Why We Should All Be Judging Books by Their Covers</title>
      <link>https://austinletson.github.io/post/bindings-and-boards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://austinletson.github.io/post/bindings-and-boards/</guid>
      <description>“We are thickly layered, page lying upon page, behind simple covers. And love - it is not the book itself, but the binding.” ― Deb Caletti
 Bindings serve three purposes. Above all, the binding enforces the order of the pages and holds the text block in place for the reader. Reading copies of books with sturdy bindings can last hundreds of years. Second to structure, the boards and the spine serve as an advertisement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking in Letters: Why Word Processors are Anti-Words</title>
      <link>https://austinletson.github.io/post/thinking-in-letters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://austinletson.github.io/post/thinking-in-letters/</guid>
      <description>“To the man who only has a hammer, everything he encounters begins to look like a nail.” ― Abraham Maslow
 Word processors have monopolized the domain of text composition for the last quarter century. At their core, these programs involve text entry at the cursor, but with this function come a peripheral of features: formatting, grammar and spell checking, support for annotation. However, the essential functionality is simple: move the cursor with the mouse or the arrow keys and type or delete letters at the cursor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>